<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on 英文文章</title><link>/en/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on 英文文章</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 16:01:23 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/en/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Jane Theme Preview</title><link>/en/post/jane-theme-preview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 16:01:23 +0800</pubDate><guid>/en/post/jane-theme-preview/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>Markdown&lt;/strong> is created by &lt;a href="http://daringfireball.net/">Daring Fireball&lt;/a>, the original guideline is &lt;a href="http://daringfireball.net/projects/markdown/syntax">here&lt;/a>. Its syntax, however, varies between different parsers or editors.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Please note that HTML fragments in markdown source will be recognized but not parsed or rendered. Also, there may be small reformatting on the original markdown source code after saving.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>AUTHOR’S POSTSCRIPT FOR THE AMERICAN EDITION</title><link>/en/post/%E5%88%98%E6%85%88%E6%AC%A3%E4%B8%89%E4%BD%93%E5%BA%8F/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 16:01:23 +0800</pubDate><guid>/en/post/%E5%88%98%E6%85%88%E6%AC%A3%E4%B8%89%E4%BD%93%E5%BA%8F/</guid><description>&lt;p>A night from my childhood remains crisply etched in my memory: I was standing by a pond before a village somewhere in Luoshan County, Henan Province, where generations of my ancestors had lived. Next to me stood many other people, both adults and children. Together, we gazed up at the clear night sky, where a tiny star slowly glided across the darkfirmament.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Math Preview中文版</title><link>/en/post/math-preview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 16:01:23 +0800</pubDate><guid>/en/post/math-preview/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.intmath.com/cg5/katex-mathjax-comparison.php">KaTeX and MathJax Comparison Demo, currently processed as KaTex&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title><link>/en/post/goisforlovers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/post/goisforlovers/</guid><description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates. This document</description></item><item><title>Biodiversity May Thrive Through Games of Rock-Paper-Scissors</title><link>/en/post/%E7%94%9F%E7%89%A9%E5%A4%9A%E6%A0%B7%E6%80%A7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/post/%E7%94%9F%E7%89%A9%E5%A4%9A%E6%A0%B7%E6%80%A7/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Recent findings add weight to the evidence that intransitive competitions between species enrich the diversity of nature.&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote></description></item></channel></rss>